<?xml version='1.0'?>

<element name='listcell'>
<documentation>http://www.xulplanet.com/tutorials/xultu/morelists.html</documentation>
<reference>http://www.xulplanet.com/reference/elemref/ref_listcell.html</reference>
  A single cell of a listbox, used for cells which contain text only.  

<attr name='crop'>
  If the label of the listcell is too small to fit in its given space, the  text will be cropped on the side specified by the crop attribute.  An ellipsis will be used in place of the cropped text. If the box  direction is reversed, the cropping is reversed.
<value name='start'>
    The text will be cropped on its left side. 
</value>
<value name='end'>
    The text will be cropped on its right side.
</value>
<value name='left'>
     (Deprecated)  The text will be cropped on its left side.
</value>
<value name='right'>
     (Deprecated)  The text will be cropped on its right side.
</value>
<value name='center'>
    The text will be cropped on both sides.
</value>
<value name='none'>
    The text will be not be cropped using an ellipsis. However, the text will
    simply be cut off if it is too large. The side depends on the CSS text
    alignment.
</value>
</attr>
<attr name='disabled' type='boolean'>
  Indicates whether the listcell is disabled or not. If this attribute is set to true,  the listcell is disabled. This is usually drawn with the text in grey. If the listcell is  disabled, it does not respond to user actions. The element cannot be focused  and the command event will not fire. The element will still respond to mouse  events. To enable the listcell, leave the attribute out entirely as opposed to  setting the value to false.
</attr>
<attr name='image' type='image URL'>
  The URL of the image to appear on the listcell. If this is attribute is left  out, no image appears. The position of the image is determined by the dir  and orient attributes. You must use the class 'listcell-iconic' to have an  image appear.
</attr>
<attr name='label' type='string'>
  The label that will appear on the listcell. If this is left out, no text appears.
</attr>
<attr name='type' type='string'>
  You can make a cell in a listbox a checkbox by setting this attribute to  the value 'checkbox'.
</attr>
<class name='listcell-iconic'>
  Use this class to have an image appear on the listcell. Specify the image  using the image attribute.
</class>
</element>
