<?xml version='1.0'?>

<element name='description'>
<documentation>http://www.xulplanet.com/tutorials/xultu/textimage.html</documentation>
<reference>http://www.xulplanet.com/reference/elemref/ref_description.html</reference>
  This element is used to create a block of text. The text can be set either  with the value attribute or by placing text inside the open and close  description tags. The value attribute is used to set text that appears in  a single line. If text appears as a child of the description, it will wrap  to multiple lines. If may contain arbitrary markup, which can be styled  as needed.  

<implements>nsIAccessibleProvider</implements>
<implements>nsIDOMXULDescriptionElement</implements>
<attr name='crop'>
  If the label of the description is too small to fit in its given space, the  text will be cropped on the side specified by the crop attribute.  An ellipsis will be used in place of the cropped text. If the box  direction is reversed, the cropping is reversed.
<value name='start'>
    The text will be cropped on its left side. 
</value>
<value name='end'>
    The text will be cropped on its right side.
</value>
<value name='left'>
     (Deprecated)  The text will be cropped on its left side.
</value>
<value name='right'>
     (Deprecated)  The text will be cropped on its right side.
</value>
<value name='center'>
    The text will be cropped on both sides.
</value>
<value name='none'>
    The text will be not be cropped using an ellipsis. However, the text will
    simply be cut off if it is too large. The side depends on the CSS text
    alignment.
</value>
</attr>
<attr name='disabled' type='boolean'>
  Indicates whether the description is disabled or not. If this attribute is set to true,  the description is disabled. This is usually drawn with the text in grey. If the description is  disabled, it does not respond to user actions. The element cannot be focused  and the command event will not fire. The element will still respond to mouse  events. To enable the description, leave the attribute out entirely as opposed to  setting the value to false.
</attr>
<attr name='value' type='string'>
  The text to be used for the description. The text will appear on a single  line and will not wrap. Normally, you would not use a value attribute on a  description element and instead place the text as the content inside the  description tag.
</attr>
<class name='header'>
  A class used for headings. Typically, this will cause the text to  appear bold.
</class>
<class name='indent'>
  This class causes the text to be indented on its left side.
</class>
<class name='monospace'>
  This class causes the text to be displayed in a monospace font.
</class>
<class name='plain'>
  This class causes the text to be displayed with no border or margin.
</class>
<class name='small-margin'>
  This class causes the text to be displayed with a smaller margin.
</class>
<prop name='accessible' type='nsIAccessible'>
  Returns the accessibility object for the description.
</prop>
<prop name='crop'/>
<prop name='disabled'/>
<prop name='value'/>
</element>
