<?xml version='1.0'?>

<element name='stringbundle'>
<documentation>http://www.xulplanet.com/tutorials/xultu/locprops.html</documentation>
<reference>http://www.xulplanet.com/reference/elemref/ref_stringbundle.html</reference>
  An element which can be used to load localized resources from property files.  Stringbundles should be placed inside a stringbundleset element.        A property file is a list of property key-value pairs each on a separate  line. The key and value is separated with an equals sign. For example, the  following defines two properties:         message.displayError=An error occured trying to display this message   message.nameAlreadyUsed=The name %s is already being used by another account.      
<html><![CDATA[
<p>  An element which can be used to load localized resources from property files.  Stringbundles should be placed inside a stringbundleset element.  </p>  <p>  A property file is a list of property key-value pairs each on a separate  line. The key and value is separated with an equals sign. For example, the  following defines two properties:  </p>  <p><pre>  message.displayError=An error occured trying to display this message<br>  message.nameAlreadyUsed=The name %s is already being used by another account.  </pre></p>  </p>
]]></html>

<attr name='src' type='string properties file URL'>
  The URL of the property file that contains the localized strings.
</attr>
<prop name='appLocale' type='nsILocale'>
  Returns the XPCOM object which holds information about the user's locale. This is  an object which implements nsILocale.
</prop>
<method name='getFormattedString' returns='string'>
<prototype> getFormattedString ( key , strArray ) </prototype>
  
  Returns a formatted string with the given key name from the string  bundle, where each occurance of %s is replaced by each successive  element in the supplied array. You may also use other formatting codes  
</method>
<method name='getString' returns='string'>
<prototype> getString ( key ) </prototype>
  
  Returns the string with the given key name from the string bundle.
</method>
<prop name='src'/>
<prop name='stringBundle' type='nsIStringBundle'>
  Returns the XPCOM string bundle object which implements nsIStringBundle.
</prop>
</element>
